ytbnet.com 2008-12-16

# YTB Travel Network

**YTB Privacy Policy**

We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. This policy covers how YTB treats personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past or current use of YTB products and services. Personal information is information that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or financial information that is not otherwise publicly available. If you are a YTB Rep and/or RTA you may edit your YTB account information at any time from your personal Back Office.

Please be aware that YTB is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other companies. This privacy statement applies solely to YTB.  We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of every website that you visit.

**Information Collection, Sharing, and Use**  
YTB uses information we receive for the following purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, conduct research, and to improve our services. 

Personal information is collected when you join YTB or use YTB products or services, when you visit YTB pages or the pages of certain YTB affiliates. YTB may combine information that we receive from business affiliates or other companies. We will never rent or sell your personal information to third parties.

Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of providing you with products and services, contacting you, or sending you emails based on your acceptance of the Independent Marketing Representative (IMR) and/or Referring Travel Agent (RTA) Terms and Conditions.  

YTB automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your web browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page(s) you access. Information is also collected about your transactions with some of our business affiliates, including information about your use of products and services we offer.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
YTB does not rent or sell your information with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you request, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * To comply with valid legal process such as subpoena, search warrant, court order, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims.
  * In order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding any illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of YTB Terms & Conditions, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, to protect the company’s rights and property, or as otherwise as required by law.

YTB may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. YTB does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad.

YTB may set and access cookies on your computer. YTB allows other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer and that use is subject to their own privacy policies. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to YTB’s cookies.

**Privacy Protection**  
We use stringent security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.

YTB utilizes physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information, including your billing and account information.

**Received Mailings**  
If you are a YTB Rep or RTA, YTB reserves the right to send you communications relating to your YTB businesses, including announcements, administrative messages, and newsletters that are considered part of your YTB account. If you received a mailing from us, your email address was listed with us when you joined YTB as an Independent Marketing Representative (IMR) and permission included as part of your IMR Terms & Conditions and/or when you joined YTB as a Referring Travel Agent (RTA) and permission included in the RTA Terms & Conditions.  Emails may contain links to other sites.

**Unsubscribe Information**  
Each email sent by YTB contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us. If you wish to unsubscribe, simply click the unsubscribe link found at the end of each email.  If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [abuse@ytb.com](mailto:abuse@ytb.com) for review.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your YTB account information (if you are a YTB Rep or RTA) or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

Effective June, 2007
